Your loan application
has been rejected.
You cannot get a loan.
Sorry.
'Meet Ayaan Kapoor.'
'Six years ago...'
- Good morning, sir.
- Good morning.
'He was rapidly climbing
the ladder of success,'
'in the world of real estate.'
- 'From dawn to dusk, he would
make deals worth millions.' - Sir.
'Except for a small glitch.'
'When it came to money,
he would be totally colour blind.'
Sir, 40% white and 60% black.
Deal?
60% black?
Sir, 80% black and 20% white.
'He had only one dream.'
'To earn enough money,'
'so one day it would be
of no value to him anymore.'
"Breaking news of the hour."
"Modiji's surgical strike
on black money."
"While announcing his
demonetisation policy, he said,"
"from midnight tonight,
1000 and 500 rupee notes
will no longer be legal tender."
'But he was unaware,'
'that his dreams would become
reality so soon.'
'Post demonetisation,'
'Ayaan's luck and property
rates took a nosedive.'
'And he was left
with millions in debts.'
'And to repay his debts,'
'he's forced to sell the mansion
he once lived in.'
Once there was a king,
just like your dad.
Welcome.
Welcome to your dream home.
Look.
German modular kitchen.
Royal mahogany wooden flooring.
And handmade artefacts
from around the world.
All that is fine,
but these artefacts have to go.
Ma'am, sir,
these are rare antique pieces.
Yeah, but they look so cheap.
Babe, guess the previous
owner had no taste at all.
Yeah, sweetheart.
Not just his taste,
his sense of Vaastu
was also pretty bad.
This door should've been facing
southeast instead of southwest.
No wonder he went bankrupt.
Oh my, God!
What happened, ma'am?
What happened?
Look at the colour of the sofa.
Baby, people are right.
You can buy a house
with money but not taste.
Excuse me.
This sofa has to go.
This has to go.
This...has to go.
This...definitely has to go.
The house is okay.
We'll let you know.
Baby, I'll be right back.
Bro, listen to me.
I heard that the previous owner
is pretty desperate to sell the place.
Because that scum's
gone bankrupt.
Ohh...
Look bro, if you can get me
this place at a cheaper rate,
I'll give you an extra commission.
Five per cent.
- Really?
- Really.
- Five per cent.
- Five per cent?
Wow!
- Hey, nice car, bro.
- Yeah.
But doesn't the colour look
too cheap?
Cheap? No.
Wait a second.
What's he doing?
This colour...has to go.
Bro, what are you doing?
Oh my, God!
What is he doing?
Aah...colour's one thing.
No sense of Vaastu either.
This mirror should be facing
southeast instead of southwest.
Bro, this mirror has to go.
No, no, no, no...
Has to go.
Five per cent extra commission
has driven him nuts.
Has to go.
This has to go.
Bro, bro, bro,
who's car are you taking apart?
Isn't this your car?
No, we came by Ola(Taxi).
Yeah.
Then...whose car is this?
Police!
Ola(Taxi)!
Come, inspector.
Look what he did to my car.
He doesn't deserve to go to jail.
He should be sentenced to life.
Listen...
Listen, I can explain.
It's a simple misunderstanding.
Listen, you can't arrest me.
Just shut up!
I said quiet.
Let's go.
Mama,
why did you handcuff papa?
I can't believe this, Ruhi.
You arrested your own husband.
You should be
thankful I was on duty.
Had it been anyone else,
you would be in jail right now.
Fine, then throw me in jail!
There is no way
you'll ever catch a criminal.
Maybe then you can get promoted.
In fact, let's do it today.
Throw me in jail.
Let's go to the police station.
Come on.
Do your job!
Relax.
I left my lunchbox inside.
I'll just go get that.
What hehe?
Sit back.
"Beloved. Beloved.
Beloved. Beloved."
Ruhi, the door.
- Ma'am, your order.
- Thank you,
- Thank you, ma'am.
- Thank you.
"You're the one I desire..."
Mom, I'm in a meeting right now.
I'll call you back later.
Bye.
"You're the comfort of my heart."
- "Take a look, sweetheart..."
- Ruhi, if mom calls,
tell her I am in a meeting.
'I see...
always lying to your mother.'
Mom?
No, mom, I had a Zoom meeting.
I know what meeting you are in.
I wonder what spell
that heroine casts on you?
No, mom, you're just...
Anyway, I don't want to talk to you.
Where is my granddaughter?
Pihu, my child.
Pihu.
Hello, grandma.
- You're too much, you know.
- Yes, I know.
Come on, get dressed.
The guests will be here soon.
Get dressed for what.
It's just my sister
and Jingaruu coming over.
I never can figure out,
why you keep calling
brother-in-law Jingaruu?
They are here.
See for yourself.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
- Love.
- How are you?
- Very good. Come.
- Hello. How are you?
- Hi, sis.
- How are you?
- Good.
- Where is Pihu?
- She's inside.
Ayaan, my favourite brother-in-law.
From the vineyards of Europe,
- Jingaruu Wine.
- Yeah.
Enjoy.
Pihu, my child.
Made in Nasik.
I can't believe you arrested him.
Guys, it's 10.
We'll have to leave in a while.
Come on, brother-in-law, so soon?
We don't live
in the city like you two.
It's a two-hour journey
all the way home.
Guys, you two make
a pretty decent living.
Why don't you buy
a place in the city?
How can we?
We spend all our salaries,
trying to fix her father's
ancestral home.
Baby, please.
You know how much
papa liked that house.
It had the reminiscences of
our grandparents.
And I burnt the whole place
down due to my stupidity.
I must restore that place
at any cost.
Papa never forgave me
while he was still alive.
If the house is restored
to its original glory,
he might forgive me from above.
Mama, I am sleepy.
- Can I tuck you in?
- Okay.
Goodnight, mom. Goodnight, dad.
Goodnight.
Guys, your sister's guilt
is costing me dearly.
I have a cheap and guaranteed idea,
to lessen her guilt.
- What is that?
- Ayaan caused that fire.
What?
We just have to say that.
- It was Diwali, right?
- Yes.
So probably it wasn't sister's
lamp that caused the fire,
rather it was Ayaan's firecracker.
And Ayaan nervously
put the blame on sister,
and he's been keeping
it a secret till now.
What say?
What nonsense?
Why should I say any of that
when it never happened?
Chill, Ayaan.
Why are you getting mad?
Sorry, I can't even get mad now.
I am living in your house,
eating your food.
Ayaan...I really am going
through terrible times.
You know...
Sometimes I feel it's not just my luck,
that's changed, you did too.
Ayaan.
What's wrong with him?
Nothing.
"Look in my eyes,"
"and you will realise."
"Whenever I try to look at me,"
"I see you instead of me."
"The world seems unfamiliar,"
"since you came along."
"I've finally learned how to live."
"I cannot live...
live when you're gone."
"I'll forsake...
forsake this world with you."
"I cannot live...
live when you're gone."
"I'll forsake...
forsake this world with you."
"O, beloved."
"Someone teach me a trick,"
"to impress you."
"If we ever drift apart,"
"I can draw you closer."
"I shall keep you in a corner
of my heart forever."
"Make you mine."
"I cannot live...
live when you're gone."
"I'll forsake...
forsake this world with you."
forsake this world after you do."
"O, beloved."
"I know you're mine forever."
"We will never part ways."
"Like two bodies,
one soul we've to be."
"O, beloved."
Ayaan, we've to buy
Pihu's birthday gift.
Yeah, but let's hurry up.
- Pihu--
- Mom, let's go get some ice cream first.
Okay.
Fine...
Mister, one chocolate ice cream.
Papa, ride.
Okay.
Hey...
Yeah...
Candy.
Mister, one candy.
Papa...popcorn.
No, Pihu.
What's this?
You've been running in every direction.
Dragging me
around for an hour!
Why can't you make up your mind?
Relax, Ayaan.
It's her birthday.
We've to buy her a gift.
What relax?
You know it's Tuesday.
I've to visit the temple.
And then I've a meeting as well.
You buy her a gift.
I am leaving.
Listen, her PTA is at 6 o'clock.
- Remember that?
- Yeah, okay.
Glory to Lord Hanuman.
"Glory to Lord Ram."
"Hail Sita-Ram."
Sir, please spare something.
"Glory to Lord Ram."
"Hail Sita-Ram."
Give that 1000 rupees platter today.
Okay, sir.
Here you go, sir.
This platter's worth 1000 rupees.
It's gone...
We haven't eaten anything
for four days, sir.
Please give us something to eat.
Aunty, even I've come here to beg.
Why don't you understand?
If He doesn't answer my prayers,
very soon
I'll be sitting next to you.
So long... Sorry.
Lord...
I've got 'Besan'
and 'Boondi' for you today.
Take whichever You like--
In fact, no need to choose.
You can have both today.
See...this is Besan.
And this is Boondi.
You can singlehandedly
lift mountains, Lord.
This is just a small deal.
Sell my home, Lord.
Sell my home.
Please alleviate your
devotee's problem, Lord.
Lord, please help me
crack this deal.
Crack this deal.
"Repeat after me..."
No...that's not Yours.
Glory to Lord Hanuman.
Welcome to your dream home.
Look. German modular kitchen.
Royal mahogany wooden flooring.
And handmade artefacts
from around the world.
Everything else is fine,
but these artefacts--
Artefacts?
They are lovely.
We like this house.
- Isn't it, baby?
- Yes, of course.
But we've a small condition.
Yes.
We want to buy this house
for our son.
Actually, he is adopted.
We don't want him to face
any problems in future.
Wow! Bravo!
What a couple!
Please take a seat.
I'll fetch the documents
from the car right away.
Yes.
Lord, I'll get four different types
of sweetmeats tomorrow.
Ball, please.
Hey, champ.
Do you know your parents are
buying this house for you?
- For me?
- Yes.
Wow!
Honestly, you are so lucky,
to be adopted by parents like them.
Am I adopted?
I am adopted?
- I am adopted!
- Yes...
Mom! Dad! I am adopted--
Chiku will be delighted.
Yes.
We'll give him the best
room in the house.
- Get in. Get in.
- Mom...
Congratulations, sir.
- Thank you. Thank you very much.
- Sign it.
I don't see our son around.
He's just a kid, after all.
And this is a huge place.
He must be feeling at home now
and playing in some corner.
Sign it.
Let me read it once.
Okay.
Yeah, everything is fine.
Then please sign.
Mom! Dad!
What happened, son?
Am I adopted?
- Who said that?
- This man did.
And then he locked me
in the bathroom.
Sign?
How could I've known,
that they haven't told
their son yet?
Sir, word on the market is
that you've gone nuts.
Finally, a client is coming to
see the house in the evening.
If you can sell the house,
then fine.
Otherwise, the bank will
even repossess your car.
Okay, what time are they coming?
6 o'clock, sir.
6 o'clock. Sh**
Don't worry, I'll be there.
I'll be there.
Okay sir.
Ruhi, I cannot come to
Pihu's PTA meeting.
Ayaan, how can you do this?
Why don't you ever understand?
Don't you know how much pressure
I am under?
Crazy guy.
Driving on the wrong way!
Bloody blind...
Hey...don't move.
Doctor, will I be okay?
Doctor?
I am not a doctor.
And you're not in surgery.
Then?
You're in make-up.
Make-up!
Yeah...look at him.
Can anyone look at him and say,
that he met with an accident
a while ago?
No. Great job, sir.
Thank you. Thank you.
But who are you guys?
- Ohh...she's angel 1.
- Hi.
- And she's angel 2.
And, I am YD.
- YD?
- YD...
- YD, who?
- Yamdoot! (Reaper)
Did you forget,
you met with an accident
a while ago?
I brought you here.
Nice try. Nice try.
Yamdoot! Angel 1!
Angel 2! Amazing.
But the effects gave you away.
You should have tried one of those,
where the door opens,
and a bright light shines through.
Maybe then I would
have believed you.
Ohh...you mean special effects.
Welcome.
Ladies and Gentlemen,
please welcome Ayaan Kapoor.
Why are you standing?
Sit down.
Angel.
Wake up, Ayaan.
It's a dream.
Wake up!
Ayaan, wake up.
This broker...
can't sell a house or drive a car.
Come, let's find out some more
details about our next contestant.
Angel.
Ayaan Kapoor.
Age; 33 years.
Born to Mr. And Mrs. Avinash Kapoor
in Mumbai.
Being the youngest in the family,
he's been the apple of his mother
and older sister's eye.
And since his childhood days,
he always dreamt of becoming
a police officer.
His dreams didn't come true,
but his girlfriend Ruhi,
who is also his wife now,
did become a police officer.
Later he tried his luck
in the world of real estate.
In the beginning, he made a fortune,
but later went bankrupt.
And today, on Tuesday evening,
at 4:36 pm, he met with an accident
with a red car.
And now he's with us.
Applause.
Wait a second.
Wait a second, dude.
What's going on here?
Who are you guys?
Didn't he tell you?
He's YD.
Yamdoot.
And I am CG.
Yamdoot? CG.
Dressed like this?
Oh, God!
He's expecting in the age
of Amazon Prime.
Son, I am CG.
You're in heaven.
I am telling you don't be scared.
We are going to play a game with you
What language are you guys speaking?
Sanskrit.
But I don't know Sanskrit.
See...
This is why we changed our appearance.
So that you people can understand.
Meaning...
am I dead?
Well...you're neither dead nor alive.
You're hanging somewhere
in the middle.
Look.
You'll be in surgery
for the next five hours.
And during that time,
we'll play a game with you.
Game?
Which game?
The Game of Life!
I am CG.
And my job is to keep an account
of a person's demerits and merits.
That's what we're going to do
in this game today.
This vessel is of your demerits,
and this one of your merits.
If you do the right
things in this game,
then people will fill your
merit vessel with white balls.
If the merit vessel fills up first,
and the white ball will fall down.
Then you will get your life back.
But if you do all the wrong things,
then people will fill the vessel
of demerit with black balls.
And if the vessel
of demerit fills up first,
and the black ball falls.
Then you'll go straight to hell.
Strange?
Game shows are trending in heaven too.
The trend started here.
You know that superstar...
The tall lad...
Remember he met with an
accident couple of years ago.
He was struggling
between life and death.
He was here too.
Such a nice man.
He came here, played the game,
won and went back.
But...he stole our idea.
And started his own
gameshow on earth.
What's his name?
KMC, sir.
- KMC.
- KMC?
Sir...
So shall we begin the game?
Listen, dude, I am not
playing any game.
I am asking you politely.
Or what?
What can you do?
Look, you cannot force me.
I have decided.
I am not playing any games.
CG, huh!
What are you doing?
Mortal being, how dare you?
Say no to me!
Tell me...
Will you play or forever burn
in the fire of hell?
Tell me!
So what have you decided?
I'll play. I'll play.
I love game shows.
Good.
So let's begin the game of life,
round 1.
Your first weakness.
You have a short temper.
You get irritated over
every little thing.
Sir, you should look at it
from my point of view.
I am bankrupt.
My house is up for sale.
Who wouldn't lose my temper
in a situation like this?
Fair enough.
So, if you had no tension in life,
you would be in a calm
and beautiful place.
Perfect holiday.
Then you wouldn't lose your temper.
Right?
Right, sir.
Then imagine you're
by a beautiful beachside.
Darling.
Reminded you of our
honeymoon, didn't it?
Yeah.
And you're looking
gorgeous, babe.
Thank you.
Remember, we had so much fun here.
What was that champagne you ordered?
The world's most expensive...
Sir.
1959 Dom Perignon.
Wow, yes.
It was this one.
- Yeah.
- Wow.
This is heaven.
Trust me, baby,
this is better than heaven.
Wow...
this night can't be
any more beautiful.
Might be possible.
Babes, just two minutes.
Yeah, I know...
I know you like candles.
I'll see you in two minutes. Bye.
Well, if I'm taking
the evening flight back,
means I'll be having dinner at home.
No, I won't eat rigid gourd.
Make some cauliflower with potatoes.
And please don't fry the cauliflower.
You fry everything.
I get fat eating them,
and later you complain
that I'm gaining weight.
Sorry, mister.
You see, network is bad
in the lift.
I'll just finish this...
And make some okra with that.
Yeah...
And make it crispy.
I know they are fried,
but this is different.
Crispy okras visibly seem more,
but it's actually less.
So you can't overeat them.
And you cannot pile on weight.
Don't teach me.
I know these things.
Yes, dessert
Can you imagine a meal
without dessert, mister?
Dessert is necessary.
No meal is complete
without a dessert.
Well, dinner is getting heavy,
so make some ice cream for dessert.
And don't talk so much,
you waste my time.
And I don't like people
who waste my time, mister.
Okay, fine.
See you later. Bye.
She talks so much.
"Going Up."
The lift didn't say it, so I did.
The lift announces...
Oh, God!
What's this?
What's what?
Why did you press the second button?
I was confused about my floor,
that's why?
Confused.
Who doesn't know which floor
they want to go to?
Wasting my time.
Ohh...I apologise, sir.
For wasting these eight seconds
of your life.
I am really sorry.
Eight seconds?
What about the entire session of
the food-food show in the beginning?
You don't seem like a busy man.
You look totally useless to me.
Let's not talk about
appearances, fatso.
You shouldn't be entering a lift.
Take the stairs.
Body shaming, huh?
Body shaming.
You're right, mister.
I should be losing weight.
You know what,
I'll go on the 13th floor too.
There's a gym here.
I'll work out and lose weight.
No, no, no.
I'll go to the 14th floor.
There's a swimming pool here.
I'll go for a swim and lose weight.
No...15th...
I'll go to the 15th floor.
It's got a sauna,
steam, and jacuzzi.
In fact, I'll go on the 16th instead.
There's a spa here.
I will feel rejuvenated.
You know what, go to
the 17th floor as well.
There is a restaurant here.
Because after all that hard work,
you'll need to stuff your face,
you hippo!
No need to go to the 17th floor.
There's a restaurant here too.
I can stuff my face here.
You go...crawling.
Why you...
Sorry.
What happened?
You were not going to lose
your temper.
But you lost control.
Look, CG...
CG sir, now you're not playing fair.
You said it will be
a perfect holiday.
But that guy was so irritating.
Who doesn't know
which floor he wants to go to?
He wouldn't stop
pressing the buttons.
I could not control myself.
What do you see?
That black dot, what else?
Exactly.
There's a giant whiteboard
in front of you,
but your attention was drawn
to this black dot.
That's your problem.
Several good things
may happen to you,
but one bad incident,
and your attention
is diverted towards it.
Audience, time for a poll.
Not a good start.
Now round 2.
Your second weakness.
Gluttony, avarice, greed.
You're full of it.
No, sir. That's not the case.
I see...
Your papa was a
professor of biology.
You used to leak his questions papers
to a student for just 2000 rupees.
What was his name?
Akshat Gupta, sir.
Those were childhood days, sir.
And papa never even
gave me pocket money.
I was compelled to do it.
One makes mistakes.
And anyway, it must have done
him some good.
He must be doing something
worthwhile today.
Yes, he's a doctor now.
Yeah, see. Doctor.
He's operating on you, see.
Akki...
Akki, don't worry.
Don't worry.
Don't worry, okay.
Don't worry,
everything is going to be fine, Akki.
It's okay. It's okay, Akki.
Sir, the patient's name
is Ayaan, not Akki.
I know. My name is Akki.
Akshat Gupta.
You talk too much.
Pass me the scalpel now.
I need to cut open the patient.
Sir, you need to patch him up,
not cut him open.
Patch him up!
Patch him up?
I am scared out of my wits.
How will I patch him up?
My head's reeling.
Call the doctor.
Sir...save me!
Sir, this idiot doesn't
know anything.
He'll slash a wrong nerve.
Please stop him.
Relax.
As I said, only one thing
can save your life.
And those are white balls.
And for that, you'll need
to perform a task.
Task? What task?
There's a couple.
Mr and Mrs. Gaikwad.
They had a bungalow in Juhu.
Five years ago, they were
in dire need of money.
The builder took advantage of this,
and purchased their
bungalow for 30 million.
30 million for a bungalow in Juhu?
You must make a deal
with that builder.
Either get them the right price,
or their house.
After all, you deal
in real estate too.
Done, sir.
I'll do it.
Great. Here.
Talk to the builder.
- Hello.
- Hello, sir.
I wanted to talk about Mr
and Mrs. Gaikwad's bungalow.
- That deal is done.
- Sir...
You know that house
is worth 150 million.
They were forced to sell it.
So what can I do?
I'll show you a better place
in the same area.
Please return
their house to them.
They are in trouble.
You'll receive merits, sir.
I am a business,
I am interested in profits,
not merits.
Please don't waste my time.
Sir...hello.
Hello, hello.
I am sorry, Ayaan.
But you failed.
CG...I tried my best.
You heard it yourself, didn't you?
He's such a lousy man,
that he didn't listen.
That scum should be getting
the black balls, not me.
You're right.
That scum should be
getting the black balls.
Audience.
CG...why did I get these black balls?
It's been five years,
maybe that's why you don't
remember Mr. and Mrs. Gaikwad.
But, you should have
recognised your own voice.
I am a business,
I am interested in profits,
not merits.
Please don't waste my time.
You snatched their home
because of your greed.
They called you several times,
but you didn't listen.
That's not all.
You robbed several other people
for your greed.
Fine, sir, I admit
I have weaknesses.
But I've already been punished.
I'm knee-deep in debts,
and my house is up for sale.
Soon I'll be out on
the streets, sir, I...
You got upset.
It's no fun this way.
Let me tell you a joke
to fix your mood.
Joke?
Why does Shobha only abuse boys?
Why?
Because abusing girls
doesn't suit Shobha.
Wasn't that funny?
Here's another one?
Why does Shobha only abuse boys?
Because abusing girls
doesn't suit Shobha.
Wasn't that funny?
One more...
Why does Shobha only abuse boys?
I laughed once.
How many times will I laugh
at the same joke?
If you can't laugh
at the same joke again,
why do you lament over
the same sorrow, my friend?
I know your house is up for sale,
but that's okay.
Life goes on,
just like our game show.
And that brings us to round three.
Your third weakness.
Jealousy.
No, sir.
That's not my weakness.
That's my strength.
I am not at all jealous, sir.
Really?
Amazing.
By the way,
your wife is pretty
attractive, isn't she?
I am sure many boys
are crazy about her.
In fact, she stays frequently
stays away from home for work.
I know what you're trying to do, CG.
But doesn't make a difference to me.
As I said...
It's my strength,
not my weakness.
I like your confidence.
I am sure you will win
white balls in this round.
All the best.
- Hi, baby.
- Hi.
What are you doing?
Don't know...
Actually, Ayaan,
I have something to tell you.
There's something
I kept a secret from you.
- Actually...it's like this...
- I know.
It's alright.
You see, to err is human.
If you unintentionally
had an affair, it's fine.
I forgive you.
The important thing is,
that we love each other.
And I'm not jealous.
I am not jealous!
Who are you talking to?
And, are you crazy?
I am not cheating on you.
I can't see beyond you anyway.
Then?
I applied for Crime Branch
without telling you.
I wanted to get in first
and then share it with you.
And guess what, I cleared it.
Yeah.
Ayaan.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Even the best of the best don't
get picked for crime branch.
And I got selected.
That's good.
What happened?
You're not happy.
No, that's not the case.
Your expressions say otherwise.
I mean,
you didn't have to rub it in.
What do you mean rub it in?
I mean...
I couldn't become a police officer,
and you're now an officer
at the crime branch.
Baby, is it my fault
if you failed your police exam?
Add some salt.
I don't have salt.
You don't?
But you are sprinkling salt
on my wounds.
And what do you mean I failed?
Are you trying to show
you're better than me?
Here's what you do.
Take this knife
and stab me all over.
And then rub this salt.
Because that's what
you're doing with your words.
Stab me, then rub salt.
Rub salt and stab me.
Stab me, then rub salt!
What happened?
You seemed pretty confident.
CG, you cheated again.
This is not jealousy.
It's married life.
Ayaan, who says jealousy comes
in only one form?
You're jealous
'of' your wife, not 'for' her.
But I am not jealous of her.
And that's your fourth weakness.
Delusion.
You have several misconceptions,
which you believe is true.
For example,
you're not jealous of your wife.
Wait a minute, sir.
It was my idea to
become a police officer.
She applied because of me.
She got in, and I didn't.
And she hasn't done anything
special as a police officer.
Did she apprehend a single
high-profile criminal,
or solve a high-profile
case to date?
There are several police officers
whose pictures feature in the newspaper.
Their names are printed in bold.
But not with her.
But, sir, if I had this opportunity,
then I would've been
the number one cop.
I would be Singham.
Singham!
Singham?
Of course.
So you can be a better
officer than your wife.
One hundred per cent sure, sir.
Want to bet?
Black balls double or nothing?
Yes. Done.
But unfortunately,
it's not possible to prove that now.
This is heaven my friend, not earth.
Everything is possible here.
Karma mirror.
This was your dream, wasn't it?
Seeing yourself in uniform.
So let's see, Mr. Singham,
what kind of police officer
do you become.
- Good morning, sir.
- Good morning.
What's the situation?
A man has taken everyone
in the bank hostage.
And inspector Tambe
is also trapped inside.
- I see...
- And, sir...
Ahh...
I will handle it.
"The heart trembles, body shivers,"
"when you know he's coming."
"Singham!"
Who is the cashier?
Me.
- Come out.
- Don't hurt me.
"Singham!"
Hands up.
Hey...stop, or I'll slit his throat.
What did you think?
You can rob a bank and escape.
Hey...don't forget.
Inspector Ayaan on duty.
- Don't worry, guys.
- Stay back!
Throw down your weapon.
Don't worry about me.
Shoot him!
How can you aim right?
Take your glasses off.
Yeah...sorry.
Don't worry, bro.
This time I will aim right.
You moved.
How can I move?
He's holding a knife to my throat.
But...
What was that?
It misfired.
Is this gun flawed?
Hey...
The flaw is in your aim,
not the gun.
You're aiming at him
and shooting me.
You know what,
aim at me and shoot him.
Yeah...
Hey, don't shoot.
Shoot! Shoot!
You let it be.
Bro, just slit my throat
and kill me.
At least it'll be an easy death.
No.
How can anyone else kill
you when I am around?
I won't let it happen.
Shut up!
Your hands are shaking.
Yes.
Take support.
- Mister...
- No...
Come on.
The police need your help.
Stand here.
Steady. Steady. Steady.
No, no, don't shoot.
Don't shoot.
Shoot. Shoot.
No...
It's all over for me.
My dreams of becoming
a father is over!
Sorry.
Singham!
Mr. CG, I've been observing.
You've not been playing fair
from the beginning.
That was a tough situation.
These things only happen in movies,
not in reality.
No, it did happen with an officer?
When? Which officer?
With your wife?
Ruhi?
Calm down.
- Calm down.
- Hey.
Don't come forward,
or I will slit his throat!
Calm down.
I said calm down.
If not about anyone else,
think about Jason.
Jason?
He's your son, isn't he?
How do you know?
His name is tattooed on your arm.
You love him, don't you?
After all, he's a motherless child.
There's a ring mark on your finger,
but no ring.
What happened?
Divorce or...
She passed away.
And now you're in some
kind of problem.
The dark circles under
your eyes indicate,
you haven't slept
for the past couple of nights.
And there are medical bills
in your pocket.
What happened?
Is Jason...
in the hospital?
Yes.
There's a hole in his heart.
Doctors have said treatment
will cost millions of rupees.
And if he's not operated on soon...
And that's why you came here.
Let's imagine
if you manage to save Jason,
do you think you can escape?
Ever imagined what will happen to a
motherless child if he loses his father too?
What do I do?
First things first,
throw down that knife.
So you can shoot me.
Okay.
- Give that to me.
- No.
You'll arrest me.
My child will be left all alone.
Look.
I'll try my best to help you.
But you'll have to trust me.
- Come on.
- No, don't come any closer.
- Stay back!
- Trust me.
Nothing will happen.
Look at me.
Come on.
I know...
I know how hard these last couple
of minutes have been for all of you.
There's nothing worse, than the feeling
of hanging between life and death.
But there is one...
Seeing your child hanging
between life and death,
which this man is experiencing.
I see criminals all day long.
But I can assure you this man
is not a criminal.
Now I'll let you'll decide
what to do with him.
It's my daughter's birthday today.
I came to withdraw money for her.
We can party another day.
But Jason's treatment is important.
Keep this money.
Keep it.
You were right.
Your wife's picture was never
featured in any newspaper.
Do you know?
She could've been on the front page of every
newspaper for saving 24 lives if she wanted to.
But she chose that father's pain.
No one filed any case.
Jason's surgery was made possible
with the money everyone donated.
Now he's absolutely fine.
That's the kind of officer
your wife is.
Anyway, what did you say?
Double or nothing.
Audience.
YD. Ever seen anyone's
vessel of sin fill up so soon?
Never, sir.
Hey, quiet, quiet.
Lord Hanuman calling.
Lord.
Hail Sri Ram, Lord.
Playing games
with the contestant, Lord.
Are you a devotee of Lord Hanuman?
Yes. A big one.
Sorry, Lord.
We didn't know.
Do you visit the temple every
Tuesday and Saturday?
Yes...
And, I don't just visit the temple,
I also offer one-litre oil every time,
along with sweets.
Made of besan and boondi.
Two options.
Two options?
Sorry, Lord.
We made a mistake.
No, no, You don't have to come over.
I'll take care, Lord.
Hail Sri Ram, Lord.
Hail Sri Ram.
You didn't tell us
you're a devotee of Lord Hanuman.
You never asked.
Remove these balls.
The Lord has ordered
us to felicitate him.
Get the materials.
Yes, get rid of these.
Come, ladies.
Ayaan, this happiness
will be too much for you.
Close your eyes.
Okay.
What is this?
Vermillion. Vermillion.
YD...
- Coins. Stick the coins.
- What's wrong?
- Yamdoot, what are you doing?
- Sticking coins.
CG? Yamdoot?
- Garland. Garland him. Oh yes, garland.
- What's wrong with him?
Stuff the sweetmeats.
Oh yes...
One more option.
Second option.
What are you doing?
Shove it in.
Now the incense sticks.
What is this way
to felicitate anyone?
Why? Didn't you like it?
No.
Then foolish human being,
who told you that God likes
your drama?
You corrupted a pious
thing like praying.
You try to bribe God,
and with options of sweetmeats?
Do you know how furious
Lord Hanuman is with you?
He was coming here personally
with his mace, to break your head.
I stopped Him.
Ayaan.
Do you know what is the biggest
mistake that humans make?
You believe in God,
but you don't listen to Him.
What does He want from you?
Humans to show some humanity.
Help each other.
But you can't do that either.
Remember that old woman,
who used to beg outside
the temple with her grandson?
No.
Did you remember this old lady?
The poor soul was starving
for four days.
She died half an hour
after you left.
"I realised as I made my way
to the temple to offer flowers,"
"that I'd murdered flowers
to please a stone."
"The place where I went
to atone for my sins,"
"I committed another one."
But don't worry,
you won't get
any black balls for this.
Because you've already
been punished for it.
Confused?
Let me explain.
Her funeral procession
left in the morning,
which caused the accident.
"Ram's name...is the ultimate truth."
Which caused a traffic jam
A cab driver got stuck and was late.
His client cancelled the ride,
and decided to catch another taxi.
Taxi.
Mom, I want a balloon.
No balloons.
- Stand quietly.
- I want it.
Just then, her daughter shrugged
her hand and started running.
The biker swerved on the wrong side
- to save the child.
- Are you mad? Driving on the wrong side.
Bloody blind...
There's a saying in English...
What goes around comes around.
As you sow, so shall you reap.
Imagine...
if you helped the old woman,
then she wouldn't have died.
It wouldn't have
caused a traffic jam,
the taxi driver wouldn't be late.
The woman wouldn't have tried
to get another taxi.
The child wouldn't be running
on the street,
and the biker wouldn't have swerved
to the wrong side.
And...
you wouldn't have met
with an accident.
This is your karma
that brought you here.
And now your karma is
taking you closer to death.
The vessel of sin is filled 98%
See...
There's still time, you can change.
Otherwise...it'll be too late.
Welcome back.
Welcome back after the break.
Ayaan, from here on,
the game will keep getting tough.
One single mistake,
and your game's over.
Angel.
But don't worry.
This time you'll get
a few lifelines.
And that's the lifeline
for this round.
You can use it if
you feel the need to.
Your fifth weakness.
Ayaan, you don't value
your relationships.
Especially women.
The women in your life.
Oh God, CG.
How many times are you going to
keep talking about my wife?
I am not talking about your wife.
I am talking about your first love.
Your first love.
She loved you so much,
but you always took her for granted.
CG, Sakshi had no reason
to be emotional.
I had made it very clear,
no strings attached.
Did I say Sakshi?
Aanchal?
Payal?
Kanika?
Is he guessing or bragging?
Of course, bragging.
Sonal?
Hit the brakes.
Let's go take a look.
Mom?
Huh...what happened, son?
Here...
No, I...
There is no one above a mother
in this world.
Her love is the ultimate.
But you don't care about Her at all.
- Mom?
- I meant Mother Goddess.
I sent you a picture
of her two days ago,
to forward to 12 people.
Did you?
Mother Goddess will curse you.
What do you think, mom?
Mother Goddess checks
everyone's WhatsApp,
whether they forwarded
the message or not.
So She can get angry over him.
One more thing.
These messages
you send me every morning--
Chances are high of
heavy black ball rains.
If the winds don't change direction,
there are possibilities
of a flood too.
I like them.
I actually love them.
My phone memory becomes full.
But it's not like I use my phone.
- Go ahead, send them.
- I see...
I thought you didn't like
them since you never replied.
Now I'll send you messages
every day.
Good morning, good afternoon,
good evening, goodnight.
I'll send you all the messages.
With flowers.
- Nice.
- Here...eat this mango.
Yes, mango.
The match has reached
a pretty interesting point.
Things are getting tougher
for Ayaan.
He has only one option left?
The envelope.
But will he use it?
One single mistake
and Ayaan's game is over.
And what do we see here?
Ayaan is going for it.
Oh my, God.
This is getting exciting.
25th April 1985.
The happiest day of my life.
Ayaan arrived in my life.
The doctor said he's
slightly underweight.
But that's okay.
He's got me.
9th October 1991.
He's six years old.
For the first time,
my son drank an
entire glass of milk.
Ayaan is weak in maths,
and I am worse than him.
I've to study for four hours myself,
so I can tutor him for one hour.
Ayaan loves watching horror films.
He likes watching it...
Mom, can I sleep with you.
And I like the part
that comes after it.
Come on. Come.
Ayaan loves mangoes.
But he doesn't like
the kernel, just like me.
Mom, I don't like the seeds.
I eat the kernels
so he doesn't have to.
Thank you, mom.
You don't always have
to eat the kernels.
Mom, now I'll eat the kernels.
This is my favourite photo
in the album.
Well done, Ayaan.
Audience.
Yes! Yes! Finally.
But, you used a lifeline.
And the price for that
is five black balls.
What?
Five black balls?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Sorry, dude.
Sometimes even
Gods make mistakes.
I'll remember this the last time.
By the way, Ayaan,
do you remember
Rocky's bachelor party?
Well, that was one crazy night.
I mean, the girls were amazing.
That night I...
Went home and slept.
Yes, yes, yes.
We know. We know.
And now, this brings us
to my favourite round.
A weakness that every man has.
Lust.
And you have to control it.
Rum three black balls
You?
What are you doing here?
I also wanted to have some fun.
So this time I am your lifeline.
I'll stop you from making
any mistakes.
No, no, I don't want any help.
Otherwise, you'll ask
for five black balls.
Last time it was just a book.
This time I came personally.
I'll charge at least 10 black balls.
10 blackballs?
Are you out of your mind?
No, just leave.
And anyway, there's one
here who I'd slip on.
So, can I leave?
No, no, wait.
Please wait here.
I...might...slip.
- Stay, please.
- Okay.
- One selfie please.
- Of course.
Do you want a selfie with Nora?
Is it allowed?
It's allowed.
- Thank you.
- It's okay.
Ma'am, one more selfie, please.
Why not?
"My eyes can't stop talking
all night long..."
"about you."
"Every time I think about you,"
"my heart skips a beat."
"Skips a beat."
"Yes, I am in love with you."
"Yes, you're my entire world."
"Lost my body and soul to you,
o gentle beloved."
"You cling on to my heart"
"Like I've known you all along"
"You seem like a Goddess,
you're most precious to me"
"I feel enchanted by you."
"My heart's lost."
"You're my desires, you're my love."
"You bring solace to my heart."
"You're my tranquillity,
you're my passion."
"You're my obsession,
you're my ecstasy."
"Can't live without you."
"Life without you is a waste."
"Yes, I am in love with you."
"Yes, you're my entire world."
"Lost my body and soul to you,
o gentle beloved."
"You cling on to my heart"
"Like I've known you all along"
"You seem like a Goddess,
you're most precious to me"
"My evenings won't be
the same without you."
"Take me in your arms,"
"make my nights beautiful."
"Never imagined
you'll be so close to me."
"Can't believe my eyes,
seems like I'm gonna die."
"This heart of mine is gradually
becoming yours."
"Look at me the way I look at you."
"Yes, I am in love with you."
"Yes, you're my entire world."
"Lost my body and soul to you,
o gentle beloved."
"You cling on to my heart"
"Like I've known you all along"
"You seem like a Goddess,
you're most precious to me"
What are you doing?
You'll die.
Do you know what's written
in the scriptures?
Always look at other women
as your sister and mother.
What?
Sister and...mother.
Mummy!
Mummy?
Loser!
Get lost!
Go ahead, laugh.
But I didn't do anything wrong.
CG, I did not cheat on my wife.
Audience.
Yes. Yes.
Yes.
Nurse, Hydropin start 0.5 quick.
Sir, we're losing him.
Get the defib.
Set the charge for 200.
Going for CPR.
Going for first. Clear.
One, two, three.
Again.
Increase to 200.
Clear.
One, two, three.
Again.
Increase to 400.
Clear.
One, two, three.
Again... three.
How is this possible?
Yeah...
This never happened before.
What do you mean by never
happened before, CG?
This is not possible.
You said I'll be fine until
I am playing the game.
I am winning now.
The white balls are piling up.
So why this?
I am sorry.
We were playing a prank.
We told a small lie.
Look.
A small lie?
Can you imagine my plight
because of this small lie?
I am really sorry.
We shouldn't have done it.
By the way, Ayaan,
have you ever done such a thing?
Where you told a lie,
and someone else had
to pay the price their entire life.
1999 Diwali.
What happened that night?
That night...
Let's go take a look.
Ayaan, I'll go give these sweets
to the neighbours.
- Okay.
- Okay, sister, hurry up.
Ayaan, how did the fire star?
Someone quickly get some water.
Hurry up.
Ayaan, how did the fire star?
Ayaan...
Why are you quiet?
Mom!
How did the fire start?
I asked what caused the fire?
It's sister's fault.
Her lamp started the fire.
No.
This house was memento
of my ancestors.
The memories of my parents.
And you burnt it down.
I will never forgive you!
Sorry, papa.
I made a mistake.
So sorry, papa. I am really sorry.
Forgive me, papa.
Please forgive me.
This was your fault,
and your sister's been living in guilt.
Time to end this guilt.
This is your last round.
Tell the truth to your sister.
Are you crazy?
If I tell her she will kill me.
There is a chance of that.
But if you don't tell her,
you'll definitely die.
We have a lifeline
for you in this round,
who will compel you
to tell the truth?
And guess what,
no black balls for this one.
No black balls?
Done.
Papa.
- Papa?
- What papa?
I've been waiting
for you to come up,
- So I can give you a thrashing.
- Papa...papa...sorry...
It's your fault.
It's your fault I was angry
with my daughter.
It's your fault.
- It's your fault.
- Sorry.
What sorry?
Say sorry to your sister.
CG, save me.
CG can't save you.
Told you.
A lifeline that will force
you to tell the truth.
This is all I have right now.
I'll pay the rest later.
Thank you, madam.
Go inside.
Come on.
- Hello, Ayaan sir.
- Hello.
Sister...
Ayaan.
You, here?
I was close-by
and thought I'll come and see you.
Sister, I had to tell you something.
Tell me.
Remember that Diwali night?
How can I forget
that night, Ayaan?
That night changed my life.
Sister, that night you
didn't cause the fire, I did.
What did you say?
Just that it wasn't your lamp
that caused the fire,
it was my firecracker.
- Sorry, sister. I was afraid.
- Ayaan...
Afraid, Ayaan?
Sorry, sister.
Do you realise
what I've been through?
All these years
I've been blaming myself.
It was your fault papa
never talked to me.
He never forgave me.
Never forgave me.
Ayaan...tell her I forgive her.
Sister, papa's saying
that he's forgiven you.
How do you know?
Tell her she doesn't have
to feel guilty.
He's saying you don't need
How do you know, Ayaan?
Tell her no need to apologise to me
every night before going to bed?
He's saying no need to apologise
to me every night before going to bed.
Ayaan, how do--
How do you know...
I apologise to papa
every night?
Well...papa came in my
dreams last night.
He scolded me and even thrashed me.
That's why I came to tell you
the truth after all these years.
Papa came in your dreams.
And...what else did papa say?
Tell her...
to stop thinking about the house.
He said you should stop
thinking about the house.
And focus on your own life.
And he said to tell brother-in-law
to stop buying Jingaruu wine.
When did I say that?
Please.
It's a pathetic wine.
Sorry.
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Hey, CG. I won! I won!
White balls.
White balls. White balls.
Yes!
Well done, Ayaan, well done.
Relax.
You were amazing.
Winning after being
on the verge of losing,
this has never happened before.
In fact, I am so pleased with you,
that along with returning your life,
I want to give you a special gift.
CG, this is...
What you couldn't do in six months,
we did it in a single day.
We sold your house.
And for 180 million.
180 million.
Meaning I'll be left with 20 million
after paying off my loans.
Thank you, CG. Thank you.
See...the benefits of earning merits.
You are absolutely right.
Now you just watch.
I'll spend the rest of
my life earning merits.
Well, then let's start from here.
I'll make an offer to you.
You can give all your white balls
to the next contestant,
and earn more merits.
No, what will I do
of so many merits?
I'll start once I go back.
Think about it.
Maybe the next contestant
is here because of you.
Because of me?
The driver...
who you had an accident with.
Did you ever think about him?
Is he the next contestant?
Maybe?
Well CG, even if he is,
he'll get a chance to play the game.
I won this game fair and square.
You're right.
Anyway, all the best.
Thank you.
You cheated, Ayaan.
You cheated.
These black balls are nothing
but your misdeeds.
As your misdeeds,
which keep growing
and spreading throughout the world.
And one day,
they grow to a point where,
you get trapped in them yourself.
I am sorry, CG.
I made a mistake.
I've a family.
A wife and a small kid.
Think about them, please.
When you don't think about them,
then why should we?
Today morning you took your daughter
for her birthday shopping.
What happened?
- Papa, popcorn?
- No, Pihu.
You've been dragging me around.
We've been going around for an hour.
Why can't you make up your mind?
Relax, Ayaan.
It's his birthday,
we've to buy her a gift.
What relax?
You know it's Tuesday.
I've to go to the temple.
And then I've a meeting.
You buy her the gift.
I am leaving.
Listen, her PTA is at 6 o'clock.
- Remember?
- Okay.
Sorry, Pihu.
Papa is a little stressed.
So don't be upset.
Come on, let's go buy
a nice gift for you.
I already got my gift.
When?
I just wanted
to spend some time with papa.
He doesn't have time
for me otherwise.
So I made an excuse for my gift.
And your wife had been
pestering you for two days.
The PTA meeting.
Actually, there is no PTA meeting.
Yes, mom, I lied to Ayaan.
He's pretty stressed nowadays.
So I wanted to take him
out for dinner.
Can you please look after Pihu?
- Okay, dear.
- Thanks, mom.
That's not all.
She knows that the bank officials
will seize your car tomorrow.
And she doesn't want
you to travel by bus.
So she is buying a new car
for you.
In fact, they all chipped in to buy
you a new car.
See.
This is my contribution.
Thank you,
brother-in-law, really.
What thank you?
Tell Ayaan to stop
calling me Jingaruu.
I am not cheap.
Excuse me.
Come and select the car, ma'am.
Yes.
Ma'am, these are the cars.
See...
- Pihu, this one?
- No.
No?
- This one?
- No.
- Pihu, this one?
- No, mama.
That car.
No...not that car.
That one?
I like this car.
Do you like this?
Hi, Ayaan.
Ruhi, I can't make it to
Ruhi's PTA meeting today.
Ayaan, how can you do such a thing?
Try to understand?
Don't you know the pressure
I am under?
Okay, fine.
Child.
That's your family.
Will...they survive?
I don't know.
Let's just hope they are good
at playing this game.
Because they have no one
to help them out.
I...I will help them.
I am there.
It's too late, Ayaan.
I gave you a chance.
The next contestants are
your wife and child.
But as always,
you chose yourself.
Time for you to go back, Ayaan.
No, CG, I cheated.
I lost.
What did I say?
If you lose, you'll go straight to hell.
There's nothing worse than seeing
your family in this condition.
Goodbye, Ayaan.
CG. CG. CG.
CG, please.
Ruhi. Pihu.
Mr. Ayaan.
Mr. Ayaan, relax. Relax.
Doctor,
how are my wife and child?
Mr. Ayaan, let us check you first.
- Relax.
- Forget about me.
- How are they, doctor?
- I'll tell you.
Calm down, relax.
They are in a coma but steady.
Unfortunately, your daughter's
kidneys are damaged.
We tried to give her
your wife's kidney,
but her body rejected it.
Then take my kidney.
- Yeah, you're a match, but...
- Doctor, please don't waste any time.
Save my daughter.
Please, doctor.
Okay, relax. Calm down.
We'll start the procedure.
- Okay.
- Doctor, can I see them?
I'll arrange for it.
Relax.
Sister, he's going to be
in a lot of pain.
I am giving you these painkillers.
But give him only one pill
at a time.
They are very strong, okay.
- Okay.
- Take care.
- Hello.
- Sir, you were amazing.
You sold the house for 180 million.
180 million?
Yes sir.
And I found this out
from the market.
Doesn't matter, sir.
Just wait and watch,
you'll rule the real
estate world again.
While trying to sell my house,
I completely ignored my family.
I don't want to waste a single second
of my life on all this.
Bye.
This way.
Mr. Ayaan.
Yes, doctor.
We have a problem.
Your wife's remaining kidney's
been infected as well.
We need two kidneys, not one.
Then arrange for it.
I've money.
I can get more if you want.
It's not about money.
It's difficult to get a
matching kidney so soon.
Then take my other kidney as well.
How will you survive
without both kidneys?
Please, doctor,
I've to save my family.
Mr. Ayaan.
Please try and understand.
We cannot do that.
It's illegal.
And unethical.
We can only take one kidney.
Please.
So...you mean to say
I'll have to choose between one.
"What delusion was my heart under,"
"couldn't understand
your importance."
"What delusion was my heart under,"
"couldn't understand
your importance."
"Now I'm here with my head bowed."
"To admit all my mistakes."
"Take my life, Lord."
"if my beloved runs out of it."
"I've given you my heart,"
"I'll even give my life."
"Never betray you, beloved."
"Swear on the Lord..."
"I've given you my heart,"
Doctor! Doctor!
Doctor, I want you
to give my kidneys...
...to my wife and child after I die.
I've signed the donor form.
"Swear on the Lord..."
"Never let these eyes
be moist again."
"Swear on the Lord..."
"Never let these eyes
be moist again."
"I am ready to face any challenge."
"Swear on the Lord..."
"I've given you my heart,"
"I'll even give my life."
"Never betray you, beloved."
I just wanted to spend some time
with papa.
"I've given you my heart,"
"I'll even give my life."
"Never betray you, beloved."
Ayaan.
Mr. Ayaan.
Well, that was a close call.
I guess someone up
there likes you a lot.
Doctor, how are Ruhi and Pihu?
Do you know what the pill
overdose did to you?
We lost you for two minutes.
You woke up after three days.
I don't care, doctor.
Why...didn't you take my kidneys?
Because we didn't need to.
We had a miracle.
Actually, we didn't know how
to save your wife and daughter.
A guy came to the hospital
with the dead body of his relative.
And can you believe it?
Both his kidneys were a match
for both of them.
Now they are okay.
Who is the guy
who brought the dead body?
I want to thank him.
I don't know. He just vanished.
He didn't tell us his name
or any other detail.
But yes, he had a locket
around his neck,
that had the initials CG.
Thank God.
"The new dawn has made
your life blossom again."
"Thank God."
Ayaan. You spent 20 million
on this house.
It was me who burnt it down.
Now you guys won't have
to stay out of the city.
- You can stay here.
- "Thank God."
My child.
Thank you.
"Thank God."
"The sigh of relief I breathed,"
"was because of You."
"The reason I just smiled,"
"was Your will."
"I haven't lost hope yet."
"All isn't lost yet."
"I can still feel you blessing me."
"The new dawn has made
your life blossom again."
"Thank God."
"I am alive..."
"As long as I am breathing."
"It's Your grace, not my right."
"You're the hand that holds me."
"Can't be seen
but you're always beside me."
"Always beside me."
"The new dawn has made
your life blossom again."
"Thank God."
One minute.
God bless you.
Thank you.
"Thank God."
"I've yet a lot to achieve,"
"but what I've achieved is enough."
Mr and Mrs. Gaikwad,
this is your home
and always will be.
Here you go.
- Forgive me.
- Thank you.
Thank you very much.
"You sent that happiness my way."
"The games that
I won were helmed by you."
"The new dawn has made
your life blossom again."
"Thank God."
"Thank you God."